<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bureo</string>

    <string name="image_description">TampaBay Image</string>
    <string name="website_icon">Website Icon</string>
    <string name="phone_number_icon">Phone Number Icon</string>
    <string name="address_icon">Address Icon</string>

    <string name="about_city">About the city</string>

    <string name="explore">Explore</string>

    <string name="tampabay_description">The hip, urban heart of Florida’s Gulf coast beats in Tampa Bay. Discover blue skies and sunshine, a sparkling waterfront, world-class chefs, family fun, and a century of Cuban culture – all in Florida’s most diverse travel destination. In Tampa Bay, our hospitality is as warm as our weather. \n \nWith cold weather in place for many, Tampa Bay is where you want to go to get nice and toasty. With its mix of historic architecture and modern landmarks, a culture infused with Cuban and Spanish flavors, vibrant business districts and beautiful waterways, Tampa is a wonderful place to work, play and unwind. \n \nTampa is known for being a great city for all ages and tastes, offering hotel accommodations that fit any budget and catering to everyone, including families, outdoor adventure seekers, and foodies and wine connoisseurs. Once known as a melting pot for all cultures and settlers, Tampa remains a welcoming place for those seeking fun, opportunity and a chance to try new things. While it’s only a short, 30-minute drive to the beaches, Tampa’s real strengths lie in its city life.</string>

    <!--Attractions Category-->
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <!--Attractions Names-->
    <string name="adventure_island_name">Adventure Island</string>
    <string name="clearwater_marine_aquarium_name">Clearwater Marine Aquarium</string>
    <string name="florida_aquarium_name">Florida Aquarium</string>
    <string name="florida_state_fairgrounds_name">Florida State Fairgrounds</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens_name">Busch Gardens Tampa Bay</string>

    <!--Attractions Descriptions-->
    <string name="adventure_island_description">Located right across the street from Busch Gardens® Tampa, Adventure Island® is 30 acres of water-drenched fun in the sun featuring the ultimate combination of high-speed thrills and tropical, tranquil surroundings for guests of all ages. Race down rapids, dig your toes into the sand or relax all day in a private cabana. New at Adventure Island, hurtle high and experience a feeling of weightlessness on Colossal Curl™, Adventure Island’s newest family thrill slide.</string>
    <string name="clearwater_marine_aquarium_description">Go beyond a typical aquarium experience and immerse yourself in the world of marine life rescue at Clearwater Marine Aquarium.  Located at Clearwater Beach, Clearwater Marine Aquarium is a unique, nonprofit rescue facility dedicated to the rehabilitation and release of marine animals. See its most notable residents, Winter and Hope stars of the popular Dolphin Tale movies. Be inspired by fun, educational presentations and exhibits with all of the resident dolphins, sea turtles, pelicans, sharks, stingrays and Walle the otter. Experience Clearwater Marine Aquarium’s important ongoing mission of conservation, rescue, rehab and release.</string>
    <string name="florida_aquarium_description">Come see why The Florida Aquarium is one of the top aquariums in the country! Experience sharks, alligators, penguins and much more! Immerse yourself in interactive programs like Dive with the Sharks, Shark Swim and Swim with the Fishes or take a Wild Dolphin Tour on board the Bay Spirit II, a 72-foot powered catamaran. Special Behind the Scenes experiences like Penguins: Backstage Pass are unique and exciting as you come face to beak with our adorable penguins. After exploring all the exhibits inside, splash away at the Aquarium\'s new water play area, The Splash Pad!</string>
    <string name="florida_state_fairgrounds_description">The Fairgrounds is home to the annual Florida State Fair, always in February, always in Tampa! Featuring free entertainment, agriculture exhibits, competitive exhibits, historical village, crafts, food, and one of the largest midways in the United States.</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens_description">Busch Gardens Tampa is a 335-acre African-themed animal theme park located in the city of Tampa, Florida. Busch Gardens Tampa is owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks and Entertainment and is their 2nd largest park in terms of attendance behind SeaWorld Orlando.</string>

    <!--Attractions Addresses-->
    <string name="adventure_island_address">10001 Mckinley Dr, Tampa,FL, 33612</string>
    <string name="clearwater_marine_aquarium_address">249 Windward Passage, Tampa, FL, 33767</string>
    <string name="florida_aquarium_address">701 Channelside Dr, Tampa, FL, 33602</string>
    <string name="florida_state_fairgrounds_address">4800 US HWY 301 N, Tampa, FL, 33610</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens_address">10165 McKinley Dr, Tampa, FL 33612</string>

    <!--Attractions Numbers-->
    <string name="adventure_island_phone_number">813 987\/5000</string>
    <string name="clearwater_marine_aquarium_phone_number">727 441\/1790</string>
    <string name="florida_aquarium_phone_number">813 273\/4000</string>
    <string name="florida_state_fairgrounds_phone_number">813 621\/7821</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens_phone_number">813 884\/4386</string>

    <!--Attractions Websites-->
    <string name="adventure_island_website">https://adventureisland.com/</string>
    <string name="clearwater_marine_aquarium_website">https://www.seewinter.com/</string>
    <string name="florida_aquarium_website">http://www.flaquarium.org/</string>
    <string name="florida_state_fairgrounds_website">http://www.floridastatefair.com/</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens_website">https://buschgardens.com/</string>

    <!--Shopping Category-->
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <!--Shopping Names-->
    <string name="international_plaza_name">International Plaza and Bay Street</string>
    <string name="tampa_premium_outlets_name">Tampa Premium Outlets</string>
    <string name="westshore_plaza_name">Westshore Plaza</string>
    <string name="westfield_citrus_park_name">Westfield Citrus Park</string>
    <string name="university_mall_name">University Mall</string>

    <!--Shopping Descriptions-->
    <string name="international_plaza_description">200 stores/16 restaurants. Neiman Marcus, Nordstrom, Dillard\'s, Tiffany and Co., Louis Vuitton, Gucci, Apple, Crate and Barrel, The Cheesecake Factory, The Capital Grille and Renaissance Hotel w/courtesy shuttle. Adjacent to Tampa International Airport.</string>
    <string name="tampa_premium_outlets_description">Tampa Premium Outlets is a 441,000 square-foot outlet shopping destination filled with over 115 retailers, delivering great brands with 25% - 65% off every day savings. Conveniently located on the intersection of I-75 and State Road 56, this outdoor shopping Center features brands including Saks Fifth Avenue OFF 5TH, Michael Kors, Coach, Polo Ralph Lauren Factory Store, Tommy Hilfiger, Under Armour, Calvin Klein and many more. Visit Simon Guest Services located in Market Hall for more information about our VIP Shopper Club and Savings Passport.</string>
    <string name="westshore_plaza_description">WestShore Plaza features Macy\'s, JCPenney, Sears, Dick\'s Sporting Goods, AMC 14 Theaters, Old Navy and over 100 specialty stores. WestShore Plaza offers dining options including Maggiano\'s, Mitchell\'s Fish Market, Seasons 52, Grimaldi\'s Pizzeria, P.F. Changs, Besito Mexican and Irish 31.</string>
    <string name="westfield_citrus_park_description">Westfield Citrus Park, formerly Citrus Park Town Center, is a shopping mall in Citrus Park, Florida, that opened in March 1999. Its four anchor stores are Dillard\'s, JCPenney, Macy\'s, and Dick\'s Sporting Goods, and it also includes a Regal Cinemas multiplex theater.</string>
    <string name="university_mall_description">University Mall, previously University Square Mall, is a shopping mall located near the University of South Florida, just north of the city limits of Tampa on Fowler Avenue; a major eight lane, east-west corridor.</string>

    <!--Shopping Addresses-->
    <string name="international_plaza_address">2223 N Westshore Blvd, Tampa,FL, 33607</string>
    <string name="tampa_premium_outlets_address">2300 Grand Cypress DR, Luz, FL, 33559</string>
    <string name="westshore_plaza_address">250 Westshore plaza, Tampa, FL, 33609</string>
    <string name="westfield_citrus_park_address">8021 Citrus Park Town Center, Tampa, FL 33625</string>
    <string name="university_mall_address">2200 E Fowler Ave, Tampa, FL 33612</string>

    <!--Shopping Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="international_plaza_phone_number">813 342\/3790</string>
    <string name="tampa_premium_outlets_phone_number">813 909\/8716</string>
    <string name="westshore_plaza_phone_number">813 286\/0790</string>
    <string name="westfield_citrus_park_phone_number">813 926\/4644</string>
    <string name="university_mall_phone_number">813 971\/3466</string>

    <!--Shopping Websites-->
    <string name="international_plaza_website">https://www.shopinternationalplaza.com/</string>
    <string name="tampa_premium_outlets_website">https://www.premiumoutlets.com/outlet/tampa</string>
    <string name="westshore_plaza_website">https://westshoreplaza.com/</string>
    <string name="westfield_citrus_park_website">https://www.westfield.com/citruspark</string>
    <string name="university_mall_website">https://www.universitymalltampa.com/</string>

    <!--Arts Category-->
    <string name="category_arts">Arts</string>

    <!--Arts Names-->
    <string name="the_dali_museum_name">The Dali Museum</string>
    <string name="glazer_childrens_museum_name">Glazer Children\'s Museum</string>
    <string name="tampa_museum_of_art_name">Tampa Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="straz_center_name">Straz Center</string>
    <string name="the_tampa_theatre_name">The Tampa Theatre</string>

    <!--Arts Descriptions-->
    <string name="the_dali_museum_description">The Salvador Dalí Museum is an art museum in St. Petersburg, Florida, United States, dedicated to the works of Salvador Dalí. It houses the largest collection of Dalí\'s works outside Europe. It is located on the downtown St. Petersburg waterfront by 5th Avenue Southeast, Bay Shore Drive, and Dan Wheldon Way.</string>
    <string name="glazer_childrens_museum_description">The Glazer Children\'s Museum is a children\'s museum located in downtown Tampa, Florida, next to the Tampa Museum of Art and Curtis Hixon Park, alongside the Tampa Riverwalk. It is part of the Waterfront Arts District.</string>
    <string name="tampa_museum_of_art_description">The Tampa Museum of Art is located in downtown Tampa, Florida. It exhibits modern and contemporary art, as well as Greek, Roman, and Etruscan antiquities.</string>
    <string name="straz_center_description">The David A. Straz Jr. Center for the Performing Arts opened its doors as the Tampa Bay Performing Arts Center, Tampa, Florida in July 1987 and has welcomed more than 16 million guests.</string>
    <string name="the_tampa_theatre_description">The Tampa Theatre is a historic U.S. theater and city landmark in the Uptown District of Tampa, Florida. The theatre features a wide range of independent, foreign, and documentary films on a daily basis.</string>

    <!--Arts Addresses-->
    <string name="the_dali_museum_address">1 Dali Blvd, St. Petersburg, FL 33701</string>
    <string name="glazer_childrens_museum_address">110 W Gasparilla Plaza, Tampa, FL 33602</string>
    <string name="tampa_museum_of_art_address">120 Gasparilla Plaza, Tampa, FL 33602</string>
    <string name="straz_center_address">1010 N Macinnes Pl, Tampa, FL 33602</string>
    <string name="the_tampa_theatre_address">711 N Franklin St, Tampa, FL 33602</string>

    <!--Arts Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="the_dali_museum_phone_number">727 823\/3767</string>
    <string name="glazer_childrens_museum_phone_number">813 443\/3861</string>
    <string name="tampa_museum_of_art_phone_number">813 274\/8130</string>
    <string name="straz_center_phone_number">813 229\/7827</string>
    <string name="the_tampa_theatre_phone_number">813 274\/8286</string>

    <!--Arts Websites-->
    <string name="the_dali_museum_website">https://thedali.org/</string>
    <string name="glazer_childrens_museum_website">https://glazermuseum.org/</string>
    <string name="tampa_museum_of_art_website">http://tampamuseum.org/</string>
    <string name="straz_center_website">https://www.strazcenter.org/</string>
    <string name="the_tampa_theatre_website">http://www.tampatheatre.org/</string>

    <!--Nightlife Category-->
    <string name="category_nightlife">Nightlife</string>

    <!--Nightlife Names-->

    <string name="ybor_city_name">Ybor City</string>
    <string name="jannus_live_name">Jannys Live</string>
    <string name="whiskey_north_name">Whiskey North</string>
    <string name="bahama_breeze_name">Bahama Breeze</string>
    <string name="hyde_park_village_name">Hyde Park Village</string>
    <string name="angry_chair_name">Angry Chair Brewing</string>
    <string name="cigar_city_name">Cigar City Brewing</string>
    <string name="ulele_name">Ulele</string>
    <string name="coppertail_name">Coppertail Brewing Company</string>
    <string name="brew_bus_name">Brew Bus Brewing</string>

    <!--Nightlife Descriptions-->
    <string name="angry_chair_description">Angry Chair Brewing is located in the heart of Seminole Heights. The tasting is open to the public and features our forward thinking beers as well as beer from other local Florida breweries.</string>
    <string name="cigar_city_description">Cigar City Brewing, makers of Jai Alai IPA® and Hunahpu’s Imperial Stout®, was founded in 2009 by Joey Redner with the goal of creating world-class beer that reflected the flavors and history of the Tampa region. This unique approach resonated with local and national markets and the brewery has quickly to produce over 90,000 barrels of beer annually. Along with Oskar Blues Brewery, Perrin Brewing, Squatters Craft Beers and Wasatch Brewery, Cigar City Brewing is a part of CANarchy, a craft brewing collective that represents the largest canned craft beer supplier in the country.</string>
    <string name="ulele_description">Located on the Tampa Riverwalk, Ulele overlooks the Hillsborough River in Tampa Heights. Serving native-inspired foods and spirits. Intricately flavored, visually appealing dishes prepared on our round 10’ barbacoa grill. Lunch and dinner served daily. On-site brewery. 400 yards from the Straz Center. Outdoor bar and outdoor seating with waterfront views. Beer and cocktails may be ordered to go and served in a special cup, which allows guests to drink legally along the 2.4-mile Tampa Riverwalk. Closed Thanksgiving and Christmas. In addition to auto, bike or pedestrian arrivals, you also can boat, canoe or kayak and dock next door at Water Works Park. A second location is at Tampa International Airport, in Airside C, with Southwest and Frontier Airlines. Please see our website for the most current menu.</string>
    <string name="coppertail_description">Enjoy Florida inspired, Tampa brewed craft beer in our tasting room. Centrally located at the crossroads of Ybor City and Downtown Tampa, celebrate happy hour or a friendly night out with our knowledgeable bartenders.</string>
    <string name="brew_bus_description">We have been sharing our love for beer since 2011 when we began our journey as a local brewery tour company. A year later we turned our tour bus into a mobile tasting room by brewing our own beer. Now, we have built a state of the art brewery and tasting room to share these awesome beers with the world. Come visit us at The Brew Bus Terminal and Tasting Room in Seminole Heights for Trivia Night, Toast Brunch, or one of our other weekly events.</string>
    <string name="ybor_city_description">Lively Ybor City is known for boutiques and vintage shops on 7th Avenue, which also hosts Cuban and Latin American eateries. The Centro Ybor mall offers indie fast food, bars, and a cinema. Housed in a 1920s bakery, Ybor City State Museum has exhibits on the cigar industry and the area’s immigrant communities. The GaYBOR district around 7th Avenue and 15th Street attracts a diverse crowd to its bars and clubs.</string>
    <string name="jannus_live_description">Jannus Live is an outdoor music venue in St. Petersburg, Florida. Located in the Downtown St. Petersburg Historic District, the courtyard venue has hosted numerous concerts for local and mainstream artists.</string>
    <string name="whiskey_north_description">Adirondack decor surrounds at this high-end nightclub with 2 levels and a packed calendar of events.</string>
    <string name="bahama_breeze_description">Laid-back chain eatery featuring Caribbean entrees and tropical cocktails amid beachy decor.</string>
    <string name="hyde_park_village_description">Hyde Park Village is an upscale open-air shopping district located in the neighborhood of Hyde Park in Tampa, Florida, United States. The center is situated in several buildings located between Swann and Rome Avenues, just a few blocks east of the SoHo district.</string>

    <!--Nightlife Addresses-->
    <string name="ybor_city_address">2015 East 7th Avenue, Tampa, FL 33605</string>
    <string name="jannus_live_address">200 1st Ave N, St. Petersburg, FL 33701</string>
    <string name="whiskey_north_address">11921 North Dale Mabry Hwy, Tampa, Florida 33618 </string>
    <string name="bahama_breeze_address">3045 N Rocky Point Dr E, Tampa, FL 33607</string>
    <string name="hyde_park_village_address">1623 W Snow Cir, Tampa, FL 33606</string>
    <string name="angry_chair_address">6401 N. Florida Ave, Tampa,FL, 33604</string>
    <string name="cigar_city_address">3924 W Spruce St, Tampa, FL, 33607</string>
    <string name="ulele_address">1810 N Highland Ave, Tampa, FL, 33602</string>
    <string name="coppertail_address">2601 E 2nd Ave, Tampa, FL, 33605</string>
    <string name="brew_bus_address">4101 N Florida Ave, Tampa, FL, 33603</string>

    <!--Nightlife Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="ybor_city_phone_number">813 274\/7936</string>
    <string name="jannus_live_phone_number">727 565\/0550</string>
    <string name="whiskey_north_phone_number">813 968\/1515</string>
    <string name="bahama_breeze_phone_number">813 289\/7922</string>
    <string name="hyde_park_village_phone_number">813 251\/3500</string>
    <string name="angry_chair_phone_number">813 690\/3599</string>
    <string name="cigar_city_phone_number">813 348\/6363</string>
    <string name="ulele_phone_number">813 999\/4952</string>
    <string name="coppertail_phone_number">813 247\/1500</string>
    <string name="brew_bus_phone_number">813 990\/7310</string>

    <!--Nightlife Websites-->
    <string name="ybor_city_website">https://yborcityonline.com/</string>
    <string name="jannus_live_website">https://www.jannuslive.com/</string>
    <string name="whiskey_north_website">http://www.whiskeynorth.com/</string>
    <string name="bahama_breeze_website">https://www.bahamabreeze.com/locations/fl/tampa/tampa/3004</string>
    <string name="hyde_park_village_website">https://www.hydeparkvillage.com/</string>
    <string name="angry_chair_website">https://angrychairbrewing.com/</string>
    <string name="cigar_city_website">https://cigarcitybrewing.com/</string>
    <string name="ulele_website">https://ulele.com/</string>
    <string name="coppertail_website">https://coppertailbrewing.com/</string>
    <string name="brew_bus_website">https://brewbususa.com/</string>

    <!--LGBT Category-->
    <string name="category_lgbt">LGBT</string>

    <!--LGBT Names-->
    <string name="bradleys_name">Bradley\'s on 7th</string>
    <string name="flamingo_resort_name">Flamingo Resort</string>
    <string name="the_honey_pot_name">The Honey Pot</string>
    <string name="enigma_name">Enigma</string>
    <string name="city_side_name">City Side</string>

    <!--LGBT Descriptions-->
    <string name="bradleys_description">Festive gay bar with a pool table, happy hours and live entertainment in a dimly-lit setting.</string>
    <string name="flamingo_resort_description">This LGBT-friendly adults-only resort is 6 miles from the beach and The Dali Museum, as well as Downtown\'s historic district.</string>
    <string name="the_honey_pot_description">Vibrant LGBT nightclub with a large dance floor and entertainment such as DJs and drag shows.</string>
    <string name="enigma_description">Lively, gay-friendly lounge with several rooms, a cozy dance floor, drag shows and sidewalk tables.</string>
    <string name="city_side_description">We have been sharing our love for beer since 2011 when we began our journey as a local brewery tour company. A year later we turned our tour bus into a mobile tasting room by brewing our own beer. Now, we have built a state of the art brewery and tasting room to share these awesome beers with the world. Come visit us at The Brew Bus Terminal and Tasting Room in Seminole Heights for Trivia Night, Toast Brunch, or one of our other weekly events.</string>

    <!--LGBT Addresses-->
    <string name="bradleys_address">1510 E city7th Ave, Tampa, FL 33605</string>
    <string name="flamingo_resort_address">3924 W Spruce St, Tampa, FL, 33607</string>
    <string name="the_honey_pot_address">1507 E 7th Ave, Tampa, FL 33605</string>
    <string name="enigma_address">1110 Central Avenue North, St. Petersburg, FL 33705</string>
    <string name="city_side_address">3703 Henderson Blvd, Tampa, FL 33609</string>

    <!--LGBT Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="bradleys_phone_number">813 241\/2723</string>
    <string name="flamingo_resort_phone_number">727 321\/5000</string>
    <string name="the_honey_pot_phone_number">813 247\/4663</string>
    <string name="enigma_phone_number">813 247\/1500</string>
    <string name="city_side_phone_number">813 350\/0600</string>

    <!--LGBT Websites-->
    <string name="bradleys_website">http://bradleyson7th.com/</string>
    <string name="flamingo_resort_website">https://www.flamingofla.com/</string>
    <string name="the_honey_pot_website">https://facebook.com/Honey-Pot-27460298048/</string>
    <string name="enigma_website">http://www.enigmastpete.com/</string>
    <string name="city_side_website">https://www.citysideloungetampa.com//</string>

    <!--Food Category-->
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <!--Food Names-->
    <string name="la_terraza_restaurant_name">La Terrazza Restaurant</string>
    <string name="eddie_sam_name">Eddie and Sam\'s N.Y. Pizza</string>
    <string name="columbia_restaurant_name">Columbia Restaurant</string>
    <string name="green_lemon_name">Green Lemon</string>
    <string name="la_teresita_restaurant_name">La Teresita Restaurant</string>

    <!--Food Descriptions-->
    <string name="la_terraza_restaurant_description">Local mainstay serving homestyle Northern Italian cuisine and wines in a warm-hued storefront space.</string>
    <string name="eddie_sam_description">Thin-crust pizza by the pie or slice made with New York water at a casual, counter-serve spot.</string>
    <string name="columbia_restaurant_description">Columbia is Florida’s Oldest RestaurantSM, founded in Tampa\'s historic Ybor City in 1905. Family-owned and operated for more than 113 years, earning acclaim for old-world charm, and award-winning Spanish/Cuban cuisine and wine list.</string>
    <string name="green_lemon_description">Modern hangout offering upbeat Mexican menu and drinks for brunch, lunch and dinner.</string>
    <string name="la_teresita_restaurant_description">Family-run eatery serving a menu of Cuban and Spanish standards in homey surroundings.</string>

    <!--Food Addresses-->
    <string name="la_terraza_restaurant_address">1729 E 7th Ave, Tampa, FL 33605</string>
    <string name="eddie_sam_address">203 E Twiggs St, Tampa, FL 33602</string>
    <string name="columbia_restaurant_address">2117 E 7th Ave, Tampa, FL 33605</string>
    <string name="green_lemon_address">915 S Howard Ave, Tampa, FL 33606</string>
    <string name="la_teresita_restaurant_address">3248 W Columbus Dr, Tampa, FL 33607</string>

    <!--Food Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="la_terraza_restaurant_phone_number">813 248\/1326</string>
    <string name="eddie_sam_phone_number">813 229\/5000</string>
    <string name="columbia_restaurant_phone_number">813 248\/4961</string>
    <string name="green_lemon_phone_number">813 868\/5463</string>
    <string name="la_teresita_restaurant_phone_number">813 879\/9704</string>

    <!--Food Websites-->
    <string name="la_terraza_restaurant_website">http://www.laterrazzayborcity.com/</string>
    <string name="eddie_sam_website">http://www.eddieandsamspizza.com/</string>
    <string name="columbia_restaurant_website">http://www.columbiarestaurant.com/</string>
    <string name="green_lemon_website">http://www.eatgreenlemon.com/</string>
    <string name="la_teresita_restaurant_website">http://www.lateresitarestaurant.com/</string>

    <!--Outdoor Category-->
    <string name="category_outdoor">Outdoor</string>

    <!--Outdoor Names-->
    <string name="clearwater_beach_name">Clearwater Beach</string>
    <string name="curtis_hixon_water_park_name">Curtis Hixon Waterfront Park</string>
    <string name="riverwalk_name">Tampa Riverwalk</string>
    <string name="sunshine_skyway_bridge_name">Sunshine Skyway Bridge</string>
    <string name="ifly_name">iFLY</string>

    <!--Outdoor Descriptions-->
    <string name="clearwater_beach_description">Angry Chair Brewing is located in the heart of Seminole Heights. The tasting is open to the public and features our forward thinking beers as well as beer from other local Florida breweries.</string>
    <string name="curtis_hixon_water_park_description">Curtis Hixon Waterfront Park is an 8-acre public park located along the Hillsborough river in downtown Tampa, Florida that opened in its current configuration in 2010. It is adjacent to the Tampa Riverwalk, Florida Museum of Photographic Arts, Tampa Museum of Art, Glazer Children\'s Museum, and Rivergate Tower.</string>
    <string name="riverwalk_description">Tampa Riverwalk is a 2.6-mile-long open space and pedestrian trail development along the Hillsborough River in Tampa, Florida.</string>
    <string name="sunshine_skyway_bridge_description">The Bob Graham Sunshine Skyway Bridge, known to locals as the Sunshine Skyway Bridge or more casually the Skyway, is a bridge spanning Tampa Bay, Florida, with a cable-stayed main span, and a total length of 21,877 feet.</string>
    <string name="ifly_description">Feel the thrill of skydiving without jumping out of an airplane. It\'s true! Head to iFLY Tampa, a premier indoor skydiving facility powered by a state-of-the-art vertical wind tunnel. After a training session, you\'ll experience free-fall conditions with the help of an instructor. No experience is necessary, and afterward, you can take home a personalized flight certificate.</string>

    <!--Outdoor Addresses-->
    <string name="clearwater_beach_address">332 S Gulfview Blvd, Clearwater, FL 33767</string>
    <string name="curtis_hixon_water_park_address">600 N Ashley Dr, Tampa, FL 33602</string>
    <string name="riverwalk_address">400 N. Ashley Dr, Ste.2125, Tampa FL 33602</string>
    <string name="sunshine_skyway_bridge_address">2I-275, St. Petersburg, FL 33711</string>
    <string name="ifly_address">10654 Palm River Rd, Tampa, FL 33619</string>

    <!--Outdoor Phone Numbers-->
    <string name="clearwater_beach_phone_number">727 562\/4825</string>
    <string name="curtis_hixon_water_park_phone_number">813 274\/8615</string>
    <string name="riverwalk_phone_number">813 274\/7744</string>
    <string name="sunshine_skyway_bridge_phone_number">727 865\/0668</string>
    <string name="ifly_phone_number">813 773\/4359</string>

    <!--Outdoor Websites-->
    <string name="clearwater_beach_website">https://visitclearwaterflorida.com/</string>
    <string name="curtis_hixon_water_park_website">https://www.tampagov.net/parks-and-recreation</string>
    <string name="riverwalk_website">https://thetampariverwalk.com/</string>
    <string name="sunshine_skyway_bridge_website">http://www.skywaybridge.com/home.htm</string>
    <string name="ifly_website">https://brewbususa.com/</string>

</resources>